Phone: (+98)9371434110 Tehran, Iran farzaadshojaei@gmail.com

Farzad Shojaei

Test Engineer

github.com/FarzaadShojaei linkedin.com/in/farzad-shojaei

SUMMERY

Each project has been a step toward excellence, showing that with the right attitude. With a background in both the technical and teamwork aspects of software projects with More than 100 thousands active users, Trying to Establish the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC), and ISTQB standards with a close working relationship maintained with technical teams. Fostering a culture of open communication and mutual respect, This involved facilitating solution-oriented discussions with product visions.

SKILLS

• Cypress •JavaScript •Git •Postman •CI/CD •Jira

WORK EXPERIENCE

Test Engineer / Mofid Securities Tehran, Iran

January 2023 — Present

Mofid Securities is Iran's largest full-service stock brokerage firm leading private investment advisory with more that 10 million active Users.

- Changed the team's working flow and methodology by holding meetings with team chapter leads and Product Owners which resulted in identifying the pain points and bottlenecks of the team.
- Created a special RTM and a Testing Checklist to examine various sections of the application in Jira based on specific needs of team.
- Formed Automation Testing and API Testing Flows From Scratch Based On RTM and Testing Checklist. leading to a **50**% **save** in testing time.
- Establishing CI/CD process, in collaboration with the Infrastructure team in **Gitlab CI**,leading to the formation of versioning workflows for both application and website.

QA Specialist / Panco.app

June 2022 — December 2022

Tehran,Iran

Pance.app The First Social Networking Platform in Iran with more than **100 thousand** active users per day, Focused on playing **mobile games** and Communicating alongside each other

- Designed over 200 test cases and scenarios considering The testing checklist for **manual testing**. resulted in finding several critical crashes in games
- Monitored Continuously the impact of the changes through metrics and feedback.
- Modernized Documentation System by Transferring Docs and rewriting Services Logs and reports to **Confluence** with the helps of Technical Teams. resulting in **Faster on-boarding time** of new joiners as reported on Technical teams KPI statistics

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Engineering, University of Science and Culture

September 2019 - June 2023

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual French: Intermediate